http://www.davidlasley.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is David Lasley’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, davidlasley.com, and other sites we own and operate.
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
Search for:
Recent Posts
How to Find the Best Concrete Contractor in your Area
Simple Ideas to Enjoy Your Balcony and Garden
The Basics of Roofing Renovations
Qualities of a Successful Entrepreneur
The Biggest Design Mistakes New Homeowners Make
Recent Comments Archives
June 2020
Roofing Services
David LasleyHow to Find the Best Concrete Contractor in your AreaSimple Ideas to Enjoy Your Balcony and GardenThe Basics of Roofing RenovationsQualities of a Successful EntrepreneurThe Biggest Design Mistakes New Homeowners Make
